A Finding Aid to the Colin de Land Collection, 1968-2008, bulk 1980-2003, in the Archives of American Art AAA.delacoli
Archives of American Art
- Photographic Material, bulk 1980-2003; 1968-2003; Series 1; 12 Linear feet Box 1-12
  - Snapshots, bulk 1980-2003; 1968-2003; 1.1
    - Mapping, Fend, Unger, Misc., 1995 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      Includes photos of the American Fine Arts exhibition Mapping: A Response to MoMA (1995), Peter Fend, book by Peter Unger and other books about international development, computer with Mapping press release in progress, Art Club 2000: A Response to Mama (incorporates photo of Colin de Land and Claudia Schiffer), Dan Graham: Back of Housing Development, Staten Island, 1978, Vito Acconci: Following Piece.
    - For Rudy Molacek, Rephotographs, 1995 January (Box 2, Folder 28-29)
      Includes rephotographed artwork and Patterson Beckwith.
    - Cape Cod, 1995 January (Box 2, Folder 30)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Peter Hutchinson, and Chi Chi.
    - Ma and [Tone?], 1995 January (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Includes photos of Pat Hearn, Jack Pierson, Aleta Hamada, Colin de Land’s aunt, Chi Chi, Shaun Caley Regen, rephotographed Renee Green poster, artwork.
    - Morse, Judd's on Spring Street, 1995 January (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Includes photos of Barbara Morse, Howard Morse, Tom Burr, Pat Hearn, Roy Arden, Moyra Davey, and Jason Simon possibly in Donald Judd’s Spring Street loft.
    - Bochner, Stockholder Studio, 1995 January (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Includes photos of Mel Bochner installing Compass: Orientation, Peter Fend, Craig Wadlin, Colin de Land, artwork by Jessica Stockholder.
    - Opening of Mapping: A Response to MoMA, 1995 January (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Includes photos of the opening reception for Mapping: A Response to MoMA (1995), with Colin de Land, Patterson Beckwith, Jack Pierson, Elizabeth Peyton, Robert Storr, Daniel McDonald, Rosalie Knox, Liz-and-Val, Peter Fend, Mariko Mori, Dennis Balk, and Howard Morse.
    - Various during Mapping: A Response to MoMA, 1995 January-February (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Peter Fend, Alice Kosmin, Mark Dion, Lisa Spellman, Ania Corcilius, unidentified woman holding The Basinger Bankruptcy Bomb New York Times headline.
    - Graham, 1995 March (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Includes photos of artwork by Dan Graham.
    - Welling/Waters Dinner, 1995 April (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Includes photos of dinner related to the American Fine Arts exhibitions My Little Movies by John Waters and The Ugly America by James Welling, Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, John Waters, Richard Prince, Jack Pierson, and Dan Graham.
    - Waters, 1995 April (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Includes photos of works from the American Fine Arts exhibition My Little Movies (1995) by John Waters.
    - Fend/Bregenz, Dion/Kunsthaus, 1995 June (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Includes photographs of Landkraft (1995) exhibition at Kunstlerhaus Palais Thurn und Taxis, Bregenz with artwork by Ocean Earth with Peter Fend, Dennis Oppenheim, George Chaikin, and Newsroom. Also includes photos of Mark Dion exhibition, including work Ursus Maritimus, Peter Fend, Barbara Morse and Howard Morse, Georg Kargl, Colin de Land.
    - Fend, Kunstlerhaus Bregenz, 1995 June (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Includes photos from Landkraft (1995) exhibition at Kunstlerhaus Palais Thurn und Taxis, Bregenz, artwork by Peter Fend, Ocean Earth Development Corporation, Dennis Oppenheim.
    - Santa Fe, 1995 July 14-18 (Box 3, Folder 11-12)
      Includes photos of Pat Hearn, Colin de Land, Paul Morris, Tom Healy, [Bob Braine?], possibly at the 1995 contemporary art fair at the Hotel La Posada-in or Hotel Santa Fe.
    - Santa Fe, Flood, 1995 July 14-19 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Includes photos of Pat Hearn and the AFA installation in Santa Fe with stolen picture marker. Also includes artwork prepared to ship and a flood at AFA.
    - Leaving for Cape Cod, 1995 August (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Includes photos of American Fine Art office area, Craig Wadlin, Patterson Beckwith, Gillian Haratani, Liz-and-Val, Isa Genzken, Colin de Land’s mother, Aleta Hamada, and his aunt, artwork.
    - Remake Vampires of Wooster and Dinner, Patti Smith, 1995 October-December (Box 3, Folder 15)
      Includes photos of Pat Hearn, Craig Wadlin, David Karlin, Gillian Haratani, Patterson Beckwith, Daniel McDonald, Colin de Land, and Chi Chi. Also includes photos of a Patti Smith concert.
    - Colin de Land, Christine Tsvetanov, 1995 November (Box 3, Folder 16)
      Includes photos of Christine Tsvetanov with police car and Colin de Land in a car. Includes additional packet of negatives.
    - CPM Opening, Esther et al, PH Storage, 1995 November (Box 3, Folder 17)
      Includes photos of opening for News and Gifts by Christian Philipp Muller, Colin de Land with camera, Christian Philipp Muller, Cathy Torsney, Barbara Morse, Howard Morse, Esther Friedman, David Karlin, Christine Tsvetanov, Daniel McDonald, and Chi Chi.
    - Misc. NYC, 1995 November (Box 3, Folder 18)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Chi Chi, Cathy Torsney, Christine Tsvetanov, Peter Fend, Tom Burr, and Daniel McDonald.
    - Burr Opening, 1995 November (Box 3, Folder 19)
      Includes photos of opening reception for Tom Burr exhibition 42nd Street Structures (1995) at American Fine Arts, with Colin de Land, Dennis Balk, Ken Cro Ken, Dan Graham, Seth Edenbaum, Howard Morse, Barbara Morse, Liz-and-Val, Esther Friedman, Peter Fend, Jack Pierson, Tom Borgese, and Daniel McDonald.
    - Ohio, 1995 November 10-12 (Box 3, Folder 20-21)
      Includes photographs of industrial setting, Colin de Land, Peter Fend at American Fine Arts.
    - Pierson Book Party, 1995 November 13 (Box 3, Folder 22-23)
      Includes photos of Jack Pierson, Pat Hearn, Cris Moor, Gillian Haratani, Peter Fend, Daniel McDonald, and Christine Tsvetanov, David Karlin, Rosalie Knox, John Waters.
    - Thanksgiving and Cape Cod, 1995 November (Box 3, Folder 24)
      Includes photos of Pat Hearn, Chi Chi, Colin de Land, Cris Moor, Daniel McDonald, Craig Wadlin, Gillian Haratani, Jack Pierson, and Chivas Clem.
    - Chateau Marmont, 1995 December (Box 3, Folder 25-26)
      Includes photos taken at the Gramercy International Contemporary Art Fair at the Chateau Marmont, Hollywood, California, with Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, John Waters, Esther Friedman, Roy Arden, Christine Tsvetanov, artwork by Art Club 2000, Mariko Mori, Mark Dion, John Waters, Moyra Davey, and Bill Owens. Also includes photos of Fama & Fortune Bulletin magazine, The Red Krayola CD. Folder 26 only includes negatives.
    - Chateau Marmont and MOCA, Los Angeles, 1995 December (Box 3, Folder 27-28)
      Includes photos taken at the Gramercy International Contemporary Art Fair at Chateau Marmont, Hollywood, California with artwork by Art Club 2000 and John Waters. Also includes photos of MOCA exhibition 1965-1975: Reconsidering the Object of Art, Pat Hearn, Christine Tsvetanov, Leslie Nolan, and Chi Chi.
    - Daytona Hat, 303 Gallery, 1995 December (Box 3, Folder 29)
      Includes photos of opening for Maureen Gallace exhibition at 303 Gallery with Colin de Land, Lisa Spellman, Daniel McDonald, Craig Wadlin, Daytona International Speedway hat, Esther Friedman, Dennis Balk.
    - Daytona Hat, 1995 December (Box 3, Folder 30)
      Envelope says: AFA Red and Green party, PB Studio, but includes two photos of the Daytona Hat. Additional negatives are included in the folder.
    - Red and Green, 1995 December 22 (Box 3, Folder 31)
      Includes two photos of Colin de Land, Nils Norman, and Cris Moor. One photo is inscribed from Jee Won Kim. Folder includes additional sheet of negatives.
    - 440 West 24th Party, 1995 December 24 (Box 3, Folder 32)
      Includes photos of a Christmas party at the de Land/Hearn home with Pat Hearn, Renee Green, Daniel McDonald, Christine Tsvetanov, Patterson Beckwith, Rosalie Knox, Rockefeller Center tree.
    - Christmas, 1995 December 28 (Box 3, Folder 33)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Aleta Hamada, Dr. Hamada, de Land’s aunt Irene, Pat Hearn, Chi Chi, Daniel McDonald, Craig Wadlin, Dennis Balk, David Karlin, Rosalie Knox, Chandler Hearn, Cris Moor, upside down Christmas tree at the de Land/Hearn apartment.
    - Skating Party, 1995 December 31 (Box 3, Folder 34)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, John Waters, Pat Hearn, Daniel McDonald, Dennis Balk, Craig Wadlin, David Karlin, Rosalie Knox, Chandler Hearn, Cris Moor, upside down Christmas tree, and Chi Chi at the de Land/Hearn apartment.
    - Various Subjects, circa 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 35)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, [Christopher Sperandio?], Craig Wadlin’s bruised leg, Jutta Koether, Dan Graham, and Jack Pierson.
    - Grand St./Wooster St., circa 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 36)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Chi Chi, Craig Wadlin, Gillian Haratani, Daniel McDonald, Cris Moor, [Matthew Antezzo?], SoHo street scenes, American Fine Arts office, artwork by Dan Graham.
    - Wooster Street, circa 1996 (Box 3, Folder 37)
      Includes photos of Wooster Street, including Pat Hearn Gallery, Joyce Goldstein Gallery, Dahn Gallery, Caren Golden Fine Art, The Drawing Center, the Performing Garage, the Wooster Group, and Brooke Alexander Gallery.
    - Various Subjects, circa 1996 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      Includes photos of Pat Hearn, Daniel McDonald, Chi Chi, [Ania Corcilius?], and concert at the Bottom Line.
    - Hohn Memorial, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 1-3)
      Includes photos of memorial for Uli Hohn at American Fine Arts, with Tom Burr, Christine Tsvetanov, Daniel McDonald, Colin de Land, Gillian Haratani, Craig Wadlin, Catherine Torsney, Rosalie Knox.
    - Kosmin Dinner, Dion Opening, 1996 January (Box 4, Folder 4)
      This envelope held two packets of photographs. Includes photos of Mark Dion creating Tar and Feathers, Craig Wadlin, Danny McDonald, Colin de Land, Mariko Mori, Knight Landesman with artwork by Peter Santino, Alice and Marvin Kosmin, David Karlin, Dennis Balk, and Reverend Jen Miller.
    - Dion Opening, 1996 January (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Includes photographs of opening reception for Mark Dion exhibition Two Trees (1996) at American Fine Arts, Mark Dion, Jackie McAllister, and J. Morgan Puett.
    - Florida Gramercy, 1996 January (Box 4, Folder 6)
      Includes photos of the Gramercy International Contemporary Art Fair at the Raleigh Hotel, Miami Beach, Florida, with Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Craig Wadlin, Carole Ramer, Esther Friedman, Daniel McDonald, Christine Tsvetanov, F.C. Gundlach, Cris Moor, Peter Fend.
    - John Waters Truck, 1996 January (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Includes photos of truck with John Waters markings, Mark Dion exhibition at American Fine Arts, Two Trees (1996), including Tar & Feathers, Rosalie Knox, Lisa Spellman, Craig Wadlin, Dan Graham, Olivier Mosset, Gillian Haratani, Daniel McDonald, and Anastasie Croy.
    - Bowling, 1996 February (Box 4, Folder 8)
      Includes photos of bowling at Bowlmor Lanes, New York, with Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Jack Pierson, Daniel McDonald, Sally McDonald, Patterson Beckwith, David Karlin, Chivas Clem, [Vaal?], [Nikis?].
    - Miscellaneous, 1996 February (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Daniel McDonald, Sally McDonald, Liz-and-Val, Cris Moor, Craig Wadlin, Gillian Haratani, Mark Dion, Christine Tsvetanov, Ira Richer, Chivas Clem, artwork by Dan Graham, poster for Art Club 2000 exhibition Clear (1994), poster for the Murmurs concert at CBGB.
    - Moyra Davey Artwork, Craig's Leg, 1996 February (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Includes photographs of Moyra Davey artwork, Craig Wadlin with bruised leg. Additional negatives of Mark Dion artwork.
    - Davey Opening, 1996 February (Box 4, Folder 11)
      Includes photos of Moyra Davey, Jason Simon, Ira Richer, Andrea Fraser, Craig Wadlin, Jackie McAllister, Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Christine Tsvetanov, and Anastasie Croy.
    - Miscellaneous, 1996 February (Box 4, Folder 12)
      Includes photos of David Carrino, Jack Pierson, Daniel McDonald, David Karlin, Christine Tsvetanov, Craig Wadlin, Chi Chi, Chivas Clem, Howard Morse, and Moyra Davey. Also includes rephotographed ads and New York street scenes.
    - Various Subjects, Spring 1996 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      Includes photos of Jane Beckwith, Pat Hearn, Gillian Haratani, Craig Wadlin, David Carrino, Alice Kosmin, Marvin Kosmin, Jack Pierson, Daniel McDonald, David Karlin, Chivas Clem, artwork by Art Club 2000, Chi Chi, a music collection, and James Dean collage.
    - Genzken, Unknown Photo Collection, Spring 1996 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      Includes photos of Pat Hearn, Chi Chi, Isa Genzken, Craig Wadlin, rephotographed unknown photo collection.
    - Misc., Porn, etc., 1996 March (Box 4, Folder 15)
      Includes photos of Sally McDonald, Christopher Sperandio, Craig Wadlin, Pat Hearn, Christine Tsvetanov, Massimo Audiello, Colin de Land, Gillian Haratani, Daniel McDonald, Times Square and SoHo street scenes, The Best Artist mural by Rene (1995).
    - Misc., Grand Street, 1996 March (Box 4, Folder 16)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Christopher Sperandio, Craig Wadlin, Ira Richer, Christine Tsvetanov, Knight Landesman, installation of Fantastic Sh*t (1996) by Simon Grennan and Christopher Sperandio at American Fine Arts, Tar and Feathers by Mark Dion, Chi Chi, AFA office walls including contact list of artists.
    - Simon Grennan and Christopher Sperandio Opening, 1996 March (Box 4, Folder 17)
      Includes photos of installation of Fantastic Sh*t (1996) by Simon Grennan and Christopher Sperandio, Reverend Jen Miller, Dennis Balk, Jackie McAllister, Christine Tsvetanov, David Karlin, and Colin de Land.
    - Grennan and Sperandio Show, Reverend Jen Miller, 1996 March (Box 4, Folder 18)
      Includes photos of women’s group visiting the Fantastic Sh*t exhibition by Simon Grennan and Christopher Sperandio, with Colin de Land, Daniel McDonald, Anastasie Croy, Craig Wadlin, Christine Tsvetanov, Reverend Jen Miller, Tom Borgese, Chi Chi, artwork by Mariko Mori and Mark Dion.
    - Dan Graham, 1996 March 20 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      Includes photos of Craig Wadlin, Colin de Land, Daniel McDonald; rephotographed photographic works by Dan Graham.
    - Grennan and Sperandio Opening, Richer Opening, 1996 March 23 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      Includes photos of Fantastic Sh*t exhibition by Simon Grennan and Christopher Sperandio, Ira Richer opening, with Patterson Beckwith, Joshua Decter, Jerry Saltz, Karen Hallock, Craig Wadlin, Anastasie Croy, Liz-and-Val, Daniel McDonald, Reverend Jen Miller, Rosalie Knox, Pat Hearn, Christine Tsvetanov, John Waters, and Colin de Land.
    - Artwork, 1996 April (Box 4, Folder 21)
      Includes photographs of artwork by a variety of artists including Sherrie Levine, Vito Acconci, Louise Lawler, Dan Graham, and Laurie Anderson. Envelope includes notes on prices and dates.
    - Mori Opening, Deitch Projects; Grennan and Sperandio Opening, 1996 April (Box 4, Folder 22)
      Includes photos of opening receptions for Made in Japan (1996) by Mariko Mori at Deitch Projects and Fantastic Sh*t (1996) by Simon Grennan and Christopher Sperandio at American Fine Arts, with Charlie Finch holding an issue of Coagula Art Journal, Daniel McDonald, Peter Fend, Richard Hoeck, [Rita Ackermann?], Tom Borgese, Gillian Haratani, Julian LaVerdiere, Colin de Land being interviewed and repairing an Ed Kienholz sculpture. Also includes Red and Green Studio photos.
    - Grennan and Sperandio Show, Jack Pierson Show, Luhring Augustine, 1996 April (Box 4, Folder 23)
      Includes photos of Jack Pierson exhibition at Luhring Augustine Gallery with Daniel McDonald, Colin de Land, and Jack Pierson; Fantastic Sh*t (1996) by Simon Grennan and Christopher Sperandio at American Fine Arts, with Tom Healy, Francesco Bonami, Craig Wadlin, Gillian Haratani, and Christine Tsvetanov. Also includes photos of the Peder Bonnier Gallery.
    - Various, Christy Turlington Postcard, 1996 April (Box 4, Folder 24)
      Includes photos of John Miller, Serge Spitzer, Cris Moor, Ed Schott, Chivas Clem, Daniel McDonald, Karen Hallock, Liz-and-Val, Patterson Beckwith, Pat Hearn, paintings by Ed Schott, Walter Robinson spin paintings opening reception, rephotographed photographs, and Tar and Feathers by Mark Dion. Also includes altered postcard of Christy Turlington Burberry ad.
    - Moor Opening, 1996 April (Box 4, Folder 25)
      Includes photos of opening reception for Cris Moor featuring Bernadette Corporation exhibition at American Fine Arts, with Colin de Land, Cris Moor, Alice Kosmin and Marvin Kosmin, Craig Wadlin, David Karlin, Chivas Clem, Gillian Haratani, Patterson Beckwith, Daniel McDonald, Tom Borgese.
    - Schnabel Party, 1996 April 13 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      Includes photos of Craig Wadlin, Cathy Torsney, artwork by Grennan and Sperandio, Christine Tsvetanov, Walter Hopps, Caroline Huber Hopps, place settings for Norman Rockwell/Jean Stein and Ruthanna Hopper plus place card clipped to photograph, Newport billboards.
    - Various Subjects, 1996 April-May (Box 4, Folder 27)
      Includes photos of Pat Hearn, Peter Fend, Jack Pierson, David Carrino, artwork by Cris Moor, SoHo street scene.
    - American Fine Arts, Gilpin Studio, 1996 May (Box 4, Folder 28)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land and George Gilpin restoring a Mark Dion tree, Craig Wadlin, Daniel McDonald, Soibian Spring, Sarah Rossiter, and Peter Fend.
    - Various Subjects, 1996 May (Box 4, Folder 29)
      Includes photos of Peter Fend exhibition at Steffany Martz Gallery, Pat Hearn, Jackie McAllister, Nils Norman, [Jason Simon?], Craig Wadlin, Eric Wadlin, Kim Levin, [Sandra Hastenteufel?], Will Rollins, Liz-and-Val, Nils Norman, [Isabelle Graw?], Mark Dion, Jack Pierson, and Christine Tsvetanov.
    - Gramercy, 1996 May 3-6 (Box 4, Folder 30-31)
      Includes photos taken at the Gramercy International Contemporary Art Fair, including Christian Nagel with Mark Dion’s Lemonade Stand, Peter Fend, Patterson Beckwith, Esther Friedman, Craig Wadlin, Daniel McDonald, Moyra Davey, Jason Simon, Pat Hearn, Colin de Land, Jackie McAllister, Mark Dion, Chi Chi and Alex Bag. Also includes photos of Annina Nosei Gallery. Negatives in Folder 31 include a larger edit.
    - American Fine Arts, 1996 May 16 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Includes photos of Peter Fend, Ruthanna Hopper, Carlo McCormick, [Jackie McAllister?], and Daniel McDonald. Also includes Colin de Land and Cris Moor installing Cris Moor featuring Bernadette Corporation exhibition.
    - Wooster Street, circa Summer 1996 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, and Chi Chi with the AFA pickup truck on Wooster Street, including a set of photos taped together.
    - White Columns Benefit, Summer 1996; Includes negatives only. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Cape Cod, Summer 1996 (Box 5, Folder 4-8)
      Includes photos of Pat Hearn, Chi Chi, Musty Chiffon, Colin de Land, Jack Pierson, Michael Thomas, Peter Hutchinson, [Marie Hearn?], Chandler Hearn, [Tom Healy?], Craig Wadlin, Daniel McDonald, David Karlin, Cris Moor, John Waters.
    - American Fine Arts, 1996 July (Box 5, Folder 9)
      Includes photos of Patterson Beckwith, Daniel McDonald, Craig Wadlin, Colin de Land, [Fahey?], rephotographed fashion photos, including images of Cris Moor and Gillian Haratini.
    - Empire State Building, Flea Market, 1996 July (Box 5, Folder 10)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Maureen Gallace, Cris Moor.
    - Various Subjects, 1996 July (Box 5, Folder 11)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Cris Moor, Bruce Fuller, and Craig Wadlin, rephotographed article in a magazine featuring Chi Chi.
    - Skoota Persol Still, 1996 July (Box 5, Folder 12)
      Includes photos of still life with Persol sunglasses and Skoota CD, Craig Wadlin, Daniel McDonald, Patterson Beckwith, Gillian Haratani, and the Drawing Center.
    - Art Club 2000 Opening, 1996 July (Box 5, Folder 13)
      Includes photos of Art Club 2000 installation and opening, Chandler Hearn holding portrait of James Meyer, Patterson Beckwith, David Karlin, Cris Moor, Lisa Spellman, Craig Wadlin, Gillian Haratani, Jack Pierson, artwork by Art Club 2000 including Untitled (Scharf Shack) After Kenny Scharf’s Scharf Schak.
    - Flood, Birthday, 1996 July 20 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      Includes photos of flooded AFA storage space, Alice and Marvin Kosmin, Pat Hearn, Gillian Haratani, Cris Moor, Daniel McDonald, Anastasie Croy, Maureen Gallace, rephotographed slides by Cris Moor.
    - Party for Cris Moor, Chi Chi Dies, 1996 July 28 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      Includes photos of Jack Pierson, Gillian Haratani, Cris Moor, David Carrino, Chivas Clem, David Karlin, memorial for Chi Chi.
    - Chi Chi RIP, Hartsdale Cemetery, NY, 1996 July (Box 5, Folder 16)
      Includes photos of Pat Hearn, Colin de Land, Chi Chi cremation.
    - Cape Cod, 1996 August (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Includes photos of Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Cris Moor, Daniel McDonald, Craig Wadlin, David Karlin, [Marion Hearn?], Sam Grubman, Paul Morris, and Jutta Koether.
    - American Fine Arts, 1996 September (Box 5, Folder 18)
      Includes photos of Olivier Mosset, Craig Wadlin, Patterson Beckwith, Daniel McDonald, Gillian Haratani, Peter Fend, Christine Tsvetanov, card for John Waters exhibition Director’s Cut (1996).
    - Bernadette Corporation Show, 1996 October (Box 5, Folder 19)
      Includes photos of Cris Moor, Pat Hearn, Patterson Beckwith, Daniel McDonald, Jack Pierson, Chivas Clem, David Karlin,and Craig Wadlin.
    - Waters Opening, 1996 November (Box 5, Folder 20)
      Includes photos of opening reception for John Waters exhibition Director’s Cut (1996) at American Fine Arts, with John Waters, Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Jack Pierson, David Karlin, Craig Wadlin, Daniel McDonald, Christine Tsvetanov, Chivas Clem, Nils Norman, Jackie McAllister, Charlie Finch, Bruce Fuller, Cathy Torsney.
    - Chateau Marmont, 1996 December (Box 5, Folder 21)
      Includes photos taken at Gramercy International Contemporary Art Fair at the Chateau Marmont, Hollywood, California, with Colin de Land, Pat Hearn, Esther Friedman, Greg Gorman, Craig Wadlin, Simon Leung.
    - Christmas, 1996 December (Box 5, Folder 22)
      Includes photos of Pat Hearn, Peter Fend, Jack Pierson, Rosalie Knox, David Karlin, Patterson Beckwith, Daniel McDonald, Jutta Koether, Jane Beckwith, and Christopher Sperandio.
    - Concert, 1996 December (Box 5, Folder 23)
      Includes photos of Jack Pierson, Tom Borgese, Colin de Land, Patterson Beckwith, Nan Goldin, Pat Hearn, Daniel McDonald, David Carrino, Mary Heilmann, Jutta Koether, John Waters, Alex Bag, concert at The Bottom Line, rephotographed ads, artwork by Sylvia Kolbowski and Christian Philipp Muller.
    - Arden O'Neill, circa 1997 (Box 5, Folder 24)
      Includes photos of crated artwork, Roy Arden, and [O’Neill?].
    - Various Subjects, circa 1997 (Box 5, Folder 25)
      Includes photos of Pat Hearn, Colin de Land, Cris Moor, Frank Schroder, Liz-and-Val, Dan Graham, Margaret Deluccia, Daniel McDonald, Aleta Hamada, Dr. Hamada, Colin de Land’s aunt, rephotographed Art Club 2000 Liberty Science Center photo, and Times Square street scenes.
    - Various Subjects, circa 1997 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      Includes photos of Pat Hearn, Daniel McDonald, Christine Tsvetanov, F.C. Gundlach, Nils Norman, Patterson Beckwith, David Karlin, artwork by Jack Pierson, Jack Pierson at work in his studio, rephotographed photographs of the Mason family and movie posters, television actors signing autographs at a convention.
    - Dan Graham Artwork, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      Includes photographs of artwork by Dan Graham: Time Delay #7 with Jeff Wall and Body Press.